http://www.scarletsweb.com/privacy-policy.php

Order today and get up and running in no time.
Register DomainYour very own website address
Transfer DomainTransfer your domain to us.
Web Hosting
Shared HostingPremium cPanel hosting Reseller HostingStart your own web hosting business
WordPress® HostingDIY with WordPress as your CMS Dedicated IP HostingGet your own IP address if you want to accept credit cards online. SSL CertificatesView our SSL Certificates
Company
Company OverviewAll about Scarlet’s Web LLC TestimonialsLots of feedback from our customer's AnnouncementsGet up to date with the latest news
DownloadsWe've compiled a selection of downloads
Affiliates
Affiliate ProgramMake money by referring your friend'
Join FreeOur affiliate program is free to join
LoginExisting affiliates login here
Support
KnowledgebaseAnswers to common questions
Contact FormSend us an email
Web Hosting
- Shared Hosting - Reseller Hosting - WordPress® Hosting - Dedicated IP Hosting - SSL Certificates
Company Overview
- Why Choose Us
- Testimonials
- Announcements
- Downloads
Affiliates
- Join Free
- Login
Support
- Submit Ticket
- View Tickets
Order Now
Privacy Policy
Affordable Website Hosting and Domain Registration - Scarlet's Web LLC > Privacy Policy
In an effort to protect our clients' and site visitors privacy and rights, Scarlet's Web LLC has established a Privacy Policy which explains what information we gather on visitors and what we do with information that we gather.
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Scarlet's Web LLC collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web site (each, a "User").
Privacy
Users' privacy is very important to Scarlet's Web LLC. We are committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to Scarlet's Web LLC.
The Information We Collect
Scarlet's Web LLC collects personally identifiable information from Users through online forms for ordering products and services. We may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site.
How We Use Information
Scarlet's Web LLC may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by Scarlet's Web LLC and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users' experience with Scarlet's Web LLC and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. At no time will Scarlet's Web LLC's database of users ever be sold to any entity for the purpose of marketing or mailing lists. Personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to our business partners without your prior consent, except that we will disclose the information we collect to third parties when, in our good faith
judgment, we are obligated to do so under applicable laws.
Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the minors is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.
Linked Internet Sites
User should be aware that other Internet sites to which User hyperlinks from the Site may contain privacy provisions that differ from the provisions provided herein. Scarlet's Web LLC is not responsible for such provisions, and expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such provisions.
×
Close
Loading...
Loading...
Close
Submit
×
Generate Password
Please enter a number between 8 and 64 for the password length
